It's your birthday party, a very special day
今天是你生日 是特别的一天
I've got a song, it won't take long, I just wanted to say
我来唱首小短歌 我只想告诉你
Happy, happy, happy, happy
祝你祝你祝你祝你
Happy, happy, happy, happy birthday to you!
祝你祝你祝你祝你生日快乐
If you wanna be the life of the party
要是你想为派对带来活力
But you're feeling just a little uptight
可你却觉得有一点拘谨
Call the doctor, beg and plead
给医生打电话 殷切请求
"Doctor, tell me what I need"
请说我缺什么
Try to put a little cheese in your knees!
只要给你的膝盖抹点起司
Bubbles and balloons
泡泡和气球
What's a birthday party
生日宴会怎能
Without bubbles and balloons?
没有泡泡和气球
Star-shaped or trapezoid
星形或者四方方
Look what I can do
样样我都会
Only Pinkie Pie can make
只有萍琪折的
A bubble shaped like you!
气球样子最像你
Just let yourself go floppy
身体软软放轻松
For now this is your chance
可别错过机会
Pretend you have no bones
就装做自己没骨架
and do the rubber chicken dance!
来跳橡皮鸡舞
Hit it, Boneless!
软骨头 来一个
Cooler than a rubber chicken
比橡皮小鸡更有趣
And tastier than cake
比蛋糕更美味
Come on, you, let's party down
你和我一起来派对
And do the Gummy shake!
像软糖摇起来
Hit it, Gummy! Uh huh! You know it! Shake it!
软糖 来一个
啊哈
没错
摇起来
'Cause I like to make you smile, smile, smile
我为你带来欢笑和欢笑
Yes I do
没烦恼
It fills my heart with sunshine all the while
仔细聆听风中笑声如银铃
Yes it does
'Cause all I really need's a smile, smile, smile
就让我见到欢笑和欢笑
From these happy friends of mine
你的快乐我收到
That's my song!
这歌是我的
What do you mean?
这是什么话
I have no idea what you're talking about
我根本听不懂你说了啥
That's it!
我受够了
Roll out the party cannon
快用派对大炮
When you hear the party cannon song
听那派对大炮的歌声
Ka-BOOM!
喀 嘣
Why should you compromise?
何必如此小气
Try this one on for size
要打就大大的
'Cause nothing quite says cheer
没有什么更惬意
Like the ringing in your ear
让它回荡耳朵里
Of the Cheese Supreme Cannonball Surprise!
就是超级起司炮弹大惊喜
Dale dale dale
跳啊跳啊跳啊
No pierdas el tino
千万看准方向
Porque si lo pierdes
要是没有看准
Pierdes el camino!
小心捅出大漏